I think all us guys
أعتقد أن جميع الأولاد هنا
should cook a meal for the girls
سيعدّون وجبة للفتيات
How should we begin and end this?
متى سيبدأون ومتى سينتهون؟
Weng Fanxi wants stir-fried vegetables
ونغ فانشي تريد خضاراً مقلية
This is our service team
هذا فريق الخدمة الخاص بنا
I'm hungry
أنا جائع
The restaurant is about to open
المطعم سيفتح قريباً
Let's not eat later
لا نأكل بعد قليل
Let's just stand here and serve them
لنقف ونخدمهن طوال الوقت
Right
نعم
Welcome
أهلاً وسهلاً
Let's decide on a slogan first
لنجهز شعارنا أولاً
Let's call it Pure Love Restaurant
فلنسميه "مطعم المودة الصادقة"
Okay, Pure Love Restaurant
ممتاز، مطعم المودة الصادقة
You'll be our manager
أنت مدير المطعم
Why should I be manager?
لماذا أنا المدير؟
Because you best represent Pure Love Restaurant
لأنك تمثل روح المطعم أكثرنا
Exactly
صحيح
The reason I like being with her
سبب أنني أحب التواجد معها
Do you know why?
تعرف لماذا؟
I wish there was someone
أتمنى أن يكون هناك أحد
who would scold me every day
يعاتبني كل يوم إلى جانبي
to push you forward
ليشجعك ويدفعك
I just want
هذا ما أريده
But actually, let me tell you
لكن دعني أخبرك
I'm a very unpredictable person
أنا شخص نشيط جداً
I know you're very unpredictable
أعرف أنك حيوي جداً
I've turned you into this
أنت أصبحت هكذا بسببي
Yes, I can't help it
صحيح، لا أستطيع غير هذا
But I also enjoy it
لكنني أستمتع أيضاً
Just indulge me
أنت تدعمني دائماً
Every day you say I don't love you
ومع ذلك تقول إنني لا أحبك
I really don't understand
حقاً لا أفهم
what love really is
ما هو الحب الحقيقي
I know
أنا أعرف
You don't love me anyway
على أي حال أنت لا تحبني
Just keep doing this then
فقط افعل هذا، يكفي
You're still saying it, aren't you?
ألست تقول ذلك أيضاً؟
You've broken my heart
لقد جرحت مشاعري كثيراً
I'll drown myself in the river, I'm telling you
سأرمي بنفسي في النهر الآن
Drown in the river
إلقاء النفس في النهر
You'll throw yourself into "Jiang's" embrace
ستلقي بنفسك في أحضان "جيانغ"
Into Jiang Shangru's embrace
إلى أحضان جيانغ شانغرو
Throw yourself to "Jiang"
إلى "جيانغ"
Is that really suicide?
وهل هذا يُسمّى انتحاراً؟
Just you wait
سأجعلك ترى!
You'll be "dead" happy
أنت سعيد للغايـة
I'll find my chance
سأجد فرصة دائماً
Just you wait
انتظر وشاهد
What's the guy going over there for?
لماذا ذهب الأولاد هناك؟
He's gone to cook for you.
ليطبخوا من أجلكن
Really?
حقاً؟
When it comes to cooking, men from the Northeast
الرجل من الشمال الشرقي في الطبخ
are absolutely top-notch.
أكيد، لا أحد أفضل منهم
Guo Xu's cooking is seriously delicious.
طبخ قو شيو لذيذ جداً
Home-style tofu.
توفو بيتي
Yeah.
نعم
Because Xiao Enya said
لأن شياو إنيا قالت
she wanted to eat home-style tofu.
أرادت أن تأكل التوفو المنزلي
Alright
حسناً
There's nothing Guo Xu can't do
لا يوجد شيء لا يجيده قو شيو
You made the poor girl faint from hunger
يستطيع أن يجعل كل الفتيات يشعرن بالجوع
Come on brothers, serve the dishes
هيا يا شباب، قدموا الأطباق
This technique looks quite powerful, Gu Zhenxiang
هذا الطبق يبدو رائعاً، قو تشنشيانغ
Not bad
جيد نوعاً ما
Compared to you
مقارنة بكم
The skill level is still somewhat lacking
مستوى الطبخ لا يزال أقل بعض الشيء
There's still a gap
هناك فرق بسيط
You can call them over for dinner now
يمكنك دعوتهن لتناول الطعام الآن
Is he here?
هل جئن؟
He's here.
وصلن
He's strolling over slowly.
لقد أتى يمشي ببطء شديد
This Jiang Shangru...
هذا جيانغ شانغرو
He'll come pick up Hu Wei soon.
سيأتي ليأخذ هو وي قريباً
What are the princesses up to?
ماذا تفعل الأميرات؟
Dressed like this?
يرتدين هذه الملابس
Princess, dinner is served.
أيتها الأميرات تفضلن إلى الطعام
This way, please.
تفضلن من هنا
Today's guest...
هذه الفتاة اليوم
Thank you.
شكراً لك
Yes, come.
نعم، تعالي
Here's an apron too.
هناك أيضاً مريول
This way, please. Come.
تفضلي من هنا
Thanks.
شكراً
Food's ready!
الطعام جاهز
Come on.
هيا تعالوا
Welcome to Pure Love Snack Bar.
أهلاً بكم في مطعم المودة الصادقة
Good work.
شكراً على تعبكم
Awesome.
رائع جداً
Great service.
الخدمة ممتازة
First, let me introduce...
أولاً، دعونا نقدم
our team lineup.
فريقنا ومهامه
Over there is the chef's station.
تلك هي منطقة الطهاة
Our team's cooking area.
قسم الطهاة عندنا
They're cooking for themselves.
هم يطهون بأنفسهم
Northeastern men.
رجل من الشمال الشرقي
Northeastern men are impressive.
رجال الشمال الشرقي ممتازون حقاً
Guo Xu's charm is showing again.
جاذبية قو شيو تبدأ بالظهور مجدداً
Chef bro.
يا أخي الطباخ
Let me refill your water.
هل أضيف لك ماء؟
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث؟
Why are you all so polite today?
لماذا أنتم مؤدبون جداً اليوم؟
Shoulder massage?
تدليك الكتف قليلاً
Okay.
حسناً
You even have this service?
وهناك خدمة كهذه أيضاً
Yes.
بالضبط
More pressure.
اضغط أكثر قليلاً
Alright.
تمام
Muscular man shoulder massage.
تدليك الأكتاف من "الرجال الأقوياء"
Not bad.
جيد أيضاً
I'll keep pouring water then.
سأتابع سكب الماء
Sure, no problem.
حسناً، لا مشكلة
Thanks.
شكراً
Dinner time!
حان وقت الأكل
Everyone, come eat!
تعالوا كلكم وتناولوا الطعام
Come eat, everyone!
تعالوا جميعاً لتناول الطعام
Everyone's back for dinner.
الجميع عاد لتناول الطعام
Okay, coming.
حسناً، حالاً
I'll sit here.
سأجلس هنا
Good work.
مشكورون على جهدكم
Okay.
حسناً
No problem, we can manage.
لا بأس، يمكننا ذلك
Amazing
مذهل حقاً
So delicious
لذيذ جداً
Those potatoes
تلك البطاطا
You stewed them
أنت من حضّرها
I can taste
لقد ذقتها
The flavors of my northeastern hometown
طعم شمالي أصيل
Perfectly stir-fried
مقلي بشكل رائع
Brother Guo Xu
يا أخي قو شيو
Are you both from Liaoning?
هل أنتما الاثنان من لياونينغ؟
Let's clink glasses
لنصطدم بالكأسين!
A big piece for you
قطعة كبيرة لك
I want a small piece
أريد قطعة صغيرة
Small piece
قطعة صغيرة
I want this one
أريد هذه
Such a tiny one
هذه صغيرة جداً
You take a big one
خذ واحدة كبيرة
I want a small piece
أريد قطعة صغيرة
Okay
حسناً
Because I'm petite
لأني جسدي صغير
Do you want potatoes?
هل تريد بطاطا؟
Let me scoop some for you
سأعطيك قليلاً
Yes
نعم، أريد
Just don't give me pork
فقط لا تضع لي لحم خنزير
Seems like there's no more potatoes
يبدو أن البطاطا نفدت
Then get me some beef instead
اطلب لي قليلاً من اللحم البقري
These potatoes are still...
هذه البطاطا ما زالت...
I don't care anymore
لا يهمني بعد الآن
You should care
بل يجب أن تهتم
This tofu is super delicious
هذا التوفو لذيذ جدا
Can you get me some tofu and that?
هل يمكن أن تعطيني توفو وهذا؟
Northeastern home-style dishes
أطباق شمالية منزلية
Does anyone want to share
في حدا يحب يشاركنا
what they consider their most meaningful trip?
أكثر رحلة حسّها كانت مميزة بحياته؟
This time
هاي المرة
Same here
معاك بنفسي
I think this is my first time
بحس هاي أول مرة
hanging out with so many complete strangers
أطلع مع هذا العدد من الغرباء
together
ونقضي وقت مع بعض
Yeah, I genuinely didn't know anyone
صح فعلاً ما بعرفهم أبداً
Actually, there's another meaning for me
وبالنسبة إلي في معنى ثاني
I feel like before,
قبل هيك كنت دايمًا
for example when you
يعني أوقات مثلاً
aren't very clear about
لما ما كنت أعرف بالضبط
what type you like
أي نوع بفضّل أو أعجب فيه
or what you want to do
أو حتى حابب شو أعمل
this time there were all kinds of different people
أما هالمرة الناس كلهم مختلفين
to choose from, right?
كأنهم يخلّوك تختار، صح؟
Not choosing
لا، مش هيك
but you suddenly
بس فجأة بتحس إنه
get this very clear
صار عندك صورة واضحة
inner expectation
عن توقعاتك بقلبك
Right
صح
I feel that
أنا بشوف
since I tend to be
لأنّي بالعادة بالشغل
more rational at work
بحتكم للعقل أكتر
so I think
عشان هيك بعتقد
this trip with everyone
لما أطلع معكم حكون
has been more emotional
أميل للمشاعر أكثر
more emotional
أكون عاطفي أكتر
It's opened up a very tender side of me
وأظهر جانبي الرقيق الحقيقي
What do you think is the most hurtful thing
برايكم وقت الخناقات
to say during an argument?
أي كلمة بتوجع أكثر؟
Let me answer first.
أنا أول أجاوب
Saying "let's break up."
لما تحكي: "خلينا ننفصل"
Casually throwing around breakup threats.
إنك تقول كلمة انفصال بسهولة
Angry words are all quite hurtful.
كل الكلام وقت العصبية بيوجع
I think this phrase is particularly hurtful:
الجملة دي بتجرح كتير
"I'm so disappointed in you."
"أنا كتير خاب أملي فيك"
Another one would be
وكمان في واحدة
"Why are you always like this?"
"ليش دايمًا أنتَ هيك؟"
"You always say things like this."
دومًا بتتلفظ بنفس الكلام
"I can't take it anymore."
ما عاد بقدر أتحمّل
Fujie,
فوجي
Fujie, think of one.
فوجي، فكّر بجملة
I can't think of any.
مش طالع معي شي
"So you just don't care at all, is that it?"
يعني ولا شي بيفرق معك؟
I don't think anything could really hurt me.
صعب ينجرح قلبي أظن
At this point in life,
هلأ تقريباً
I'm all about emotional stability.
بعيش باستقرار نفسي
All about that emotional stability.
كتير أعتمد على هدوئي
Nice.
رائع
Do you have any?
وإنتَ عندك شي؟
Yes.
عندي
For example,
مثلاً
"I just can't understand
عنجد ما بفهم
how I ended up with you."
كيف بكون معاك أصلاً؟
That hurts
مؤلمة
Extremely devastating
وجعها قوي كتير
So painful
عنجد بتوجع
Absolutely brutal
لا يُعلى عليها
Hearing this makes me sad
لو سمعت هيك بجد بزعل
These words are quite heartbreaking
الكلام دا بجد يضايق
Zheng Dedong is a man with a past
جندي رجل عنده قصص
We were having a happy meal
الأكل كان ممتع بالبداية
Then you suddenly ask this
فجأة تطرح هذا السؤال
Now I'm reminiscing about my life
وبعدها شريط الحياة يدوّر براسي
Let's just enjoy our meal first
خلينا حالياً نفرح ونستمتع بالأكل
Don't let these questions
لا تطرح هيك أسئلة هلأ
ruin the mood later
عشان ما نجيب طاقة سلبية
Are you about to cry?
في حدا حيبكي قريباً؟
Yes
صح
My food doesn't taste as good now
الأكل طعمُه تغير فجأة
Let me ask if you'd mind
أسأل سؤال كمان، هل بزعجكم
your partner having
لو شريك حياتكم
a romantic history
كان عنده تجارب حب قبل؟
that's particularly extensive?
وكانت كتيرة؟
I'm not dating their exes
أنا مش عم أواعد حبيبه أو حبيبته السابقة
How many exes they have is none of my business
قديش لديه علاقات سابقة ما بهمني
Doesn't matter to me
مو فارقة معي
Actually with more
وأصلاً كل تجربة
relationship experience
بتخليه أو بتخليها
she becomes more mature
أنضج بالمشاعر
I think that's not bad
بالعكس مش إشي سلبي
Makes getting along easier
هيك سهل تتعامل معه
Did you have a crush on any girls before?
كان عندك إعجاب سري ببنت قبل؟
Me?
أنا؟
You probably made your feelings obvious, right?
أنت أصلاً دايمًا إعجابك معلن
I always...
دايمًا كدة
...made sure everyone knew who I liked.
الكل بيعرف مين اللي عاجبتني
But I'd never actually tell the girl...
بس عمري ما باعترف لها
...that I liked her.
إني معجب فيها
Though everyone else would know.
بس الكل بيعرف
Right.
صح
I'd tell everyone around her...
بحكي للكل حواليها
...but never say it to her directly.
لكن مستحيل أخبرها مباشرة
In middle school, I had a crush on a boy.
أنا لما كنت صغيرة كنت معجبة بولد
During cleaning duty...
وأيام مناوبة التنظيف
...while sweeping...
وقت نكنّس الصف
I'd deliberately position myself near him.
أتعمد أظل جمبه دومًا
Like when fetching or changing rags...
أو لما نرجّع أدوات التنظيف
I'd engineer "accidental" meetings.
أعمل حالي بمصادفة جنبه
I'd wait for him to return...
أوقف أستناه يرجع
...just to catch another glimpse.
بس مشان أشوفه نظرة زيادة
But what made me lose interest later...
بس بعدها قل حماسي تجاهه
...was realizing he hadn't grown taller from 7th to 9th grade.
لأنه من أول إعدادي لآخرها ما طول أبداً
I'm somewhat similar to you.
أنا زيّك شوي
I'm somewhat similar to her.
أنا وهي عندنا شبه
When crushing on a guy...
لو أعجبت بولد
My eyes would probably...
عيني بتصير تراقبه على طول
We're the same
زيّنا الاثنين بالضبط
Aries people really are all alike
يبدو برج الحمل كلهم زي بعض
Truly
فعلاً
Our expressions may look forward
حتى لو ملامحنا عادية
But our eyes
عيوننا دائمًا بتروح عليه
Aries' crushes are all the same
كل إعجابات الحمل شكلها واحد
So obvious, your crushes
واضح جدًا إعجابكم
Their laughter is synchronized too
حتى ضحكتكم متوافقة
"Help"
"الحقوني"
Mention Fu Jie
اذكر فوجي
Ask if he's ever had a crush
اسأله إذا بيحب سرا
Fu Jie, who would you crush on?
فوجي، مين أعجبت في سرك؟
Any crushes today?
واليوم عندك إعجاب بحدا؟
Ask if he's ever had a crush
اسأله إذا أعجب مرة
Ever had a crush?
سبق وأعجبت بحدا؟
Have you?
صح؟
Probably
أعتقد نعم
Yes
إيه عندي
But you never showed it
يعني ما عبرت؟
No
أبدًا
No, never showed it
أبدًا ما عبرت
I like buying toys for my cat
بحب أشتري ألعاب لقطتي
But I end up playing with them myself
بس كل مرة أنا بلعب فيهم مش هي
Because they never play
هم أصلاً ما بيحبوا اللعب
Cat toys are cute
ألعاب القطط لطيفة جدًا
I used to love browsing dog toys too
أنا كمان كنت أشتري ألعاب للكلب
Playing with dogs
وأقضي وقت مع الكلب
Every day I'd go out
كل يوم أطلع
And bring back a new one
أرجع بلعبة جديدة له
It was so happy
هو ينبسط كتير
Dogs love playing
الكلاب تحب الألعاب
But cats don't like toys
أما القطط ما تلعب أبدًا
Right
صح
Cats only play with interactive things
القطط تلعب فقط بالأشياء التفاعلية
Or things they shouldn't play with
أو أشياء مش مخصصة للعب أصلاً
Paper balls, trash
ورق مكور أو زبالة
My rubber bands
أو حتى رباط شعري
And straws
أو الشفاطة
They play with such weird stuff
ألعابهم غريبة فعلًا
They only play with forbidden things
يلعبوا بس بالأشياء الغلط
Let's thank the chefs.
خلينا نشكر الطباخين
Thank you.
شكرًا
Thanks, chef.
شكرًا للطباخ
Let's go.
يلا نمشي
Are you looking at the far end of the sea?
عم تتطلع على البحر من بعيد؟
I'm trying to see where that hotel is.
قاعدة أبحث وين الفندق أصلاً
Which hotel?
أي فندق؟
You mean the hotel you're staying at?
تقصدوا فندقنا؟
Our hotel is very far away.
فندقنا فعلاً بعيد جداً
Can't see it.
مش مبين من هون
It's in a very distant place.
بمكان شديد البعد
Can you see our hotel then?
يعني ممكن نشوف فندقنا؟
We're in Sanya.
إحنا في سانيا
It's far from here.
بعيد كتير من هون
You're in Sanya?
أنتم بسانيا
We're at
وإحنا بـ
Shenzhou Peninsula.
شبه جزيرة شنجو
Can you two stop being so in sync?
ممكن تبطلوا هاي المزامنة بينكم؟
Not very comfortable.
مش مريح بصراحة
He's uncomfortable now.
صار مش مرتاح
Then just don't let him be comfortable.
خليه يضل مو مرتاح وبس
Can't be comfortable every day anyway.
ما في راحة كل يوم أصلاً
Right?
مو هيك؟
Gu Zhenxiang ate chili today.
قو تشنشيانغ أكل فلفل اليوم
So spicy.
لهالدرجة كان حار؟
That's spicy already?
هذا بس اللي صار؟!
Attention all island residents,
انتباه أيها سكان الجزيرة
The third partner mission is about to begin.
مهمة الشراكة الثالثة ستبدأ حالاً
This is the final chance to compete for off-island invitation rights.
هذه آخر فرصة للفوز بحق موعد خارج الجزيرة
Now announcing the rules for the third partner pairing.
سنعلن الآن قواعد اختيار الشركاء للجولة الثالثة
This pairing will be mutual selection between genders.
هذه المرة الشراكة باختيار متبادل بين البنات والأولاد
Residents must choose from childhood photos
على السكان أن يختاروا من صور الطفولة
to select their most desired opposite-sex partner.
شخصاً من الجنس الآخر يرغبون بتكوين فريق معه
Only mutual selections will result in successful pairing.
إذا تم الاختيار المتبادل يتم تكوين الشراكة
I'm done for.
انصدمت
I never expected
لم أكن أتوقع هذا
that childhood photos would be used this way.
لم أعرف أن اختيار صور الطفولة سيكون له كل هذا التأثير
Depends how young the photos are.
حسب كم كانت الصورة قديمة
Right.
صحيح
If they're too young, how would you choose?
لو كانت الصورة لطفل صغير جداً كيف نعرف من هو؟
Mine should be easy to recognize.
صورتي وأنا طفل سهلة المعرفة
She'll definitely pick me.
أعتقد أنها ستتعرف علي فوراً
I trust her.
أنا واثق منها
Mine aren't much different.
أنا أيضاً لم أتغير كثيراً
First, female residents please proceed to the photo area
أولاً، على الفتيات التوجه إلى منطقة الصور
to make your selections.
اختاروا الآن
My childhood photos are terrifying.
صورتي وأنا صغيرة كانت مرعبة
I was raised like a boy when I was little.
تم تربيتي كصبي وأنا صغيرة
"Help me"
"النجدة"
Who is who here?
من هذا أصلاً؟
What is this?
ما هذا الشيء؟
Who's this?
من هذا؟
How...how do I choose?
كيف أختار من هنا؟
This must be Daniel.
هذا أكيد دانييل
This one looks like him too.
هذه الصورة أيضاً تشبهه
This is Zheng Dedong.
هذا تشنغ ده دونغ
No, this is Fu Jie.
لا، هذا فوت جيه
This is Fu Jie.
هذا فوت جيه
Quite handsome.
وسيم فعلاً
I think it's Fu Jie.
أعتقد أنه فوت جيه
I'm done for, I'm really done for.
مصيبة، أنا فعلاً ضعت
This one's really handsome.
هذا جميل جداً
This is Daniel, right?
هذا دانييل صح؟
I think this is Daniel.
أعتقد أن هذه الصورة لدانييل
I think this is Jiang Shangru.
أظن أن هذه الصورة لجيانغ شانغرو
This is Jiang Shangru.
هذا جيانغ شانغرو
Jiang Shangru looks just like this when he smiles.
هذا يشبه جيانغ شانغرو وهو يبتسم
That one is Jiang Shangru.
تلك لجيانغ شانغرو
This one looks like a girl.
هذه الصورة تبدو لفتاة
I think this one is Tao Zhi.
أظن أن هذه الصورة لتاو تشي
This is Gu Zhenxiang.
هذه قو تشن شيانغ
Really?
حقاً؟
That melancholic expression.
هذه النظرة الحزينة
Gu Zhenxiang.
قو تشن شيانغ
He's had those melancholic eyes since childhood.
ملامحه حزينة منذ الطفولة
He still looks like this now.
ولا يزال كذلك حتى الآن
Big eyes.
بعيون واسعة
And those melancholic eyebrows.
وعيناه مليئتان بالحزن
So I looked at the photo.
لهذا نظرت للصورة جيداً
And I thought it was him.
وظننت أنه هو
So I chose that photo.
فاختارت صورته
What is this?
ما هذا الشيء؟
Who is this?
من هذا؟
This is Guo Xu.
هذا قوه شو
Really handsome.
وسيم فعلاً
Guo Xu?
هل هو قوه شو؟
He said he was a 200-pound kid when he was little.
قال إنه كان سميناً جداً عندما كان صغيراً
How did it grow so big?
كيف صار بهذا الشكل؟
How is it so huge?
كيف تغير هكذا؟
We're doomed.
مصيبة
Xiao Enya, don't pick the wrong one.
شياو إنيا، لا تخطئي في الاختيار
Look carefully, pay attention.
دققي جيداً وانتبهي
One of these two is Tao Zhi.
واحدة من هاتين الصورتين هي تاو تشي
This must be Tao Zhi.
هذه تاو تشي على الأغلب
I think this one looks like it.
أشعر أن هذه تشبهه
This one resembles it.
هذه الصورة تشبهه
I'll choose this one.
سأختار هذه
This is Zheng Dedong.
هذه صورة تشنغ ده دونغ
Zheng Dedong is this one.
تشنغ ده دونغ هو هذا
Really?
حقاً؟
This is Daniel.
هذه لدانييل
This one is Daniel.
نعم، هذه لدانييل
This one's Daniel.
هذه صورة دانييل
Time to choose
انتهى وقت الاختيار
Female islanders, please return to the tents
على البنات العودة إلى الخيمة
Male islanders, proceed to the photo area
ويتوجه الأولاد إلى منطقة الصور
I’ll pick instantly
سأختار في لحظة
Instant pick—me too
اختيار فوري، وأنا أيضاً
I knew at a glance
عرفت فوراً من الصورة
Because he asked me to find one
لأنه طلب مني أعثر على صورة
A really tiny one
تكون قديمة جداً
So I picked one where
فبحثت عن صورة
I barely recognized myself
حتى أنا لم أتعرف على نفسي فيها
I’ve looked like this since I was two and a half
منذ كنت في الثانية ونصف أبدو كما الآن
But I worry he’ll pick an even younger one
لكن أخشى أن يختار صورة لي أصغر سناً
Since I shared it
لأنني أرسلتها له
This grouping is fun
هذه الطريقة في التقسيم ممتعة جداً
This is fun
هذا ممتع فعلاً
So fun
فعلاً ممتع
This is really fun
الأمر ممتع جداً
Everyone’s experience is different
كل واحد يشعر بالتجربة بشكل مختلف
I really want to see which photo they picked
أريد حقاً أن أعرف أي صورة اختاروا
Let’s go
لنذهب
Oh no
ضاع كل شيء
Call the police
بلغوا الشرطة
How to choose?
كيف نختار؟
Can’t pick at all
من المستحيل الاختيار
We’re doomed
انتهى الأمر
How do we choose?
كيف نختار من هذه؟
How? How do we choose?
كيف أختار؟ ما العمل؟
How to choose
كيف أختار من هنا؟
How to choose? Who is this?
كيف أختار؟ من هذا أصلاً؟
They say who this is
يقولون: من هذا؟
They can't recognize any of them
لا يستطيعون التعرف على أي أحد
"Help"
"أنقذوني"
Unbelievable, I give up
استسلمت فعلاً
I'm speechless
استسلمت تماماً
It's over
ضاع كل شيء
I think they'll definitely pick wrong
أظن أنهم سيخطئون حتماً في الاختيار
This is a boy, right?
هذا ولد، أليس كذلك؟
Is this a boy?
هل هذا ولد حقاً؟
This one's really hard to guess
الاختيار هنا صعب جداً
Yeah
صحيح
Only elimination method left
يجب أن نستخدم طريقة الاستبعاد
Elimination method
طريقة الاستبعاد
This is that...
هذه لذاك الشخص
Chen Meng'er
تشنغ منغ إر
This is obviously Chen Meng'er
واضحة جداً، إنها تشنغ منغ إر
I think this should be...
أظن أن هذه يجب أن تكون ...
I found it
وجدتها
He found it
لقد وجدها
Guo Xu found it
قوه شو وجدها
Can you tell who this is?
هل يمكنك معرفة من في هذه الصورة؟
So tiny, this one
هذه لصغير جداً
This kinda looks like Weng Fanqian
تشبه ونغ فان شي قليلاً
No, I think Weng Fanqian is this one
لا، أظن أن هذه هي ونغ فان شي
This doesn't look like Weng Fanqian
هذه لا تشبه ونغ فان شي
This bald head
هذه صورة بدون شعر
Whose bald head?
لمن هذه الصورة بدون شعر؟
I think this is Hu Wei
أظن أن هذه لهو وي
This is an easy choice
هذه سهلة الاختيار
She has big eyes
عيناها واسعتان جداً
I think her mouth... that lip shape
أظن أن شفتيها ... شكل الشفتين
I don't think this looks like Hu Wei
أظن أن هذه ليست لهو وي
You should trust my intuition, okay?
ثق بحدسي، حسناً؟
It's fine
لا مشكلة
This one... this one definitely is
هذه، هذه بالتأكيد ...
She's had boys liking her since childhood, you know
كان الأولاد معجبين بها من الصغر
Who's this motorcycle rider?
من هذه التي تقود الدراجة؟
Chen Mengjia, right?
ربما تشنغ منغ جيا
Yes, this might be Chen Mengjia
نعم، ربما هي تشنغ منغ جيا
Chen Mengjia
تشنغ منغ جيا
This is Chen Mengjia
هذه تشنغ منغ جيا
This is definitely Chen Mengjia
هذه بالتأكيد تشنغ منغ جيا
Chen Mengjia
تشنغ منغ جيا
No doubt about this one
لا يوجد أي غموض هنا
Then I'll choose Chen Mengjia
إذاً سأختار تشنغ منغ جيا
Impressive
رائع
This is truly impressive
هذا حقاً مذهل
Why is this so difficult?
لماذا هو صعب لهذه الدرجة؟
This one's a bit tricky
هذا صعب قليلاً
I think it might be this one
أظن أنه ربما هذه
Could it be...
هل من الممكن أن تكون؟
For this type, I feel we can only use elimination
هنا يمكننا فقط استخدام طريقة الاستبعاد
Who's this?
من هذه؟
This kinda looks like Zheng Dedong
لماذا تشبه قليلاً تشنغ ده دونغ؟
A little bit
فعلاً فيها شبه
This one looks like Zheng Dedong
هذه تشبه تشنغ ده دونغ
Kind of similar
تشبهه قليلاً
Somewhat resembles Zheng Dedong
تشبه تشنغ ده دونغ قليلاً
Really looks like Zheng Dedong
تشبه تشنغ ده دونغ فعلاً
Truly similar
فعلاً تشبهه
Destined to be
مكتوبة من القدر
Just pick this one
اختاري هذه الصورة إذن
You should choose this one
اختاري هذه
Okay
حسناً
Alright
موافق
Because that photo
لأن تلك الصورة
Really does look like a little boy
تبدو حقاً لطفل صغير
And I did have some guesses
وكان لدي بعض التخمينات
About which one might be Weng Fanxi
أي صورة ستكون لوينغ فان شي
I was making guesses
كنت فقط أخمن
But I truly couldn't guess who it was
لكن لم أستطع التعرف على أحد فعلاً
I couldn't tell at all
لا أستطيع معرفة أي أحد
Which one are you choosing?
أي واحدة ستختارين؟
I'll pick this one
سأختار هذه
Fu Jie is still looking
فوت جيه لا يزال يبحث
I have no choice, I can only pick this one
ما عندي حل آخر، مضطر لاختيار هذه
Because everyone else
لأن الجميع
The other guys were very confident
الأولاد الآخرون كانوا واثقين جداً
And took the photos they wanted
وأخذوا الصور التي أرادوها
So I was left with (the last one)
فبقيت لي صورة واحدة فقط
I have absolutely no idea who that is
ولا أعرف أبداً لمن هذه الصورة
The matching results will be announced shortly
سيتم إعلان نتائج الأزواج قريبًا
All island residents please gather at the photo area
يرجى من الجميع التوجه إلى منطقة الصور
Let's see if Jiang Shangru chose correctly
دعونا نرى هل اختار جيانغ شانغرو بشكل صحيح
I don't even dare to think
لا أجرؤ حتى على التفكير
I don't dare to think either
ولا أنا أجرؤ على التفكير أيضًا
Did you choose correctly?
هل اخترت بشكل صحيح؟
Not sure
لا أعلم
I think you guys
أعتقد أنكم أيها الشباب
definitely all chose wrong
من المؤكد أنكم اخترتم خطأ
I got it right, 100% correct
أنا اخترت صح، متأكد مئة بالمئة
Can you tell which one is me?
هل تعرف أي صورة لي؟
You're too easy to recognize
أنت سهل التعرف عليك جدًا
You're too obvious
أنت واضح جدًا
Way too obvious
واضح للغاية
Who's the hardest to recognize?
من الأصعب في التعرف؟
The bald one is the hardest
الأصلع هو الأصعب
Am I easy to recognize?
هل من السهل التعرف علي؟
Very easy to pick
من السهل جدًا الاختيار
It's the eyes and
العينان و...
eyes, face shape, mouth
العينان، شكل الوجه، والفم
grew proportionally
كل شيء كبر بنفس النسبة
I was raised as a boy when young
عندما كنت صغيرة، ربوني كصبي
But you have fangs
لكن لديك ناب صغير
I'm not smiling
لم أبتسم
You are smiling
لقد ابتسمتِ
Oh no
انتهى الأمر
Full of confidence
واثق جدًا
Absolutely confident
ثقة تامة
I had fangs when I was little
كنت أمتلك ناب عندما كنت صغيرًا
He chose wrong
لقد اختار خطأ
He even kissed that photo earlier
لقد قبّل الصورة لتوه
Seeing the fangs reminded me of her
عندما رأيت الناب تذكرتها
Adorable
لطيفة
You better not choose wrong
فقط لا تخطئ في الاختيار
I'm telling you
اسمعني جيدًا
If I'm wrong I'll jump in the sea, I swear
لو اخترت خطأ سأقفز في البحر
He said while kissing it
كان يقبل الصورة ويقول
If he's wrong he'll jump in the sea
لو أخطأ سيقفز في البحر
Here it comes, sea jump
حان وقت القفز في البحر
About to jump in the sea
سوف يقفز في البحر الآن
Full of confidence
ثقة تامة
Absolutely confident
مليء بالثقة
Guo Xu
قوه شو
Guo Xu shows up
قوه شو، أظهر نفسك
This is me
هذه صورتي
That's hilarious
مضحك للغاية
Her little fang
نابها الصغير ذلك
This must be
هذه بالتأكيد...
Definitely looks like Lu Wanfei
واضح أنها لو وانفي
Was that you?
هل هذه أنتِ؟
You picked the wrong person
لقد أخطأت في اختياري
And even gave a kiss
بل وقمت بتقبيلها
Gave a kiss
وقبلتها أيضًا
Go away
ابتعد
Total social suicide moment
موقف إحراج اجتماعي كامل
But no one expected
لكن لم يتوقع أحد
Xiao Enya's photo
أن صورة شياو أنيا هذه
To look just like a boy
تبدو وكأنها لصبي
Such a contrast
مفاجأة غريبة جدًا
Go jump in the sea and wash yourself off quickly.
اذهب بسرعة واغتسل في البحر
"You're unclean now."
"أصبحت غير نقية الآن"
Then whose photo did Zheng Dedong take?
من يحملها تشنغ ديدونغ إذن؟
That's me.
هذه صورتي
That's you.
آه، هذه أنتِ
No, this was the only one left in the end.
لا، كانت هذه الأخيرة المتبقية فقط
Then they all said it looks like me.
ثم قالوا جميعًا إنها تشبهني
The more I look, the more it resembles me.
كلما نظرت إليها أشبه نفسي أكثر
You know what?
هل تعلمين؟
It really does look like you.
حقًا تشبهك
It truly resembles you.
نعم، فعلاً تشبهك
You really couldn't guess this.
هذا شيء يصعب تخمينه
This isn't your fault.
ليس ذنبك
You're all so dumb.
أنتم أغبياء للغاية
No, not this one.
لا، هذه...
Mine is actually difficult.
صوري صعبة التمييز
Whose photo did Daniel take?
من يحملها دانيال؟
Weng Fanxi.
وِنغ فانشي
It's Weng Fanxi.
نعم، إنها ونغ فانشي
Zheng Dedong, which one is your childhood photo?
تشنغ ديدونغ، أي صورة لك وأنت صغير؟
The black one, all dark and unclear.
السوداء، داكنة جدًا
Right, you can barely see anything.
نعم، لا تظهر بوضوح
Why did you choose this one of me?
لماذا اخترت صورتي هذه؟
Does this look like me?
هل تشبهني هذه الصورة؟
Fu Jie
فو جيه
No, this was the only one left.
لا، كانت الأخيرة المتبقية فقط
Who is this?
لمن هذه الصورة؟
This is He Jinyi.
هذه صورة هي جين يي
Why is He Jinyi crying?
لماذا تبكي هي جين يي؟
Because I drank that yogurt.
لأنني شربت ذلك اللبن
I asked my dad to get it for me.
طلبت من والدي أن يمسكه لي
I went to the bathroom.
ذهبت إلى الحمام
When I came out, my dad had finished it.
وعندما خرجت، كان والدي قد شربه كله
So I got upset.
شعرت بالغضب
Who is this?
لمن هذه؟
That's Daniel, right?
أعتقد أنها دانيال
Daniel.
دانيال
Daniel was so handsome as a child.
كان دانيال وسيمًا وهو صغير
So handsome.
وسيم جدًا
To be honest,
بكل صراحة
I think Daniel is the most handsome.
أرى أن دانيال الأوسم بينهم
Indeed.
حقًا صحيح
This childhood photo of Daniel is really handsome.
صورة دانيال وهو صغير رائعة فعلًا
Among childhood photos, Daniel's is the most handsome.
من بين صور الطفولة، دانيال هو الأوسم
Too handsome.
وسيم للغاية
I don't remember when this was taken.
لا أذكر متى تم التقاطها
Looks like a child star.
يبدو نجمًا طفلاً
Now announcing the final partner pairing results.
والآن نعلن نتائج الأزواج النهائية
Congratulations.
مبروك
Chen Mengjia and Gu Zhenxiang.
تشنغ مينغجيا وقو تشنشيانغ
Hu Wei and Jiang Shangru.
هو وي وجيانغ شانغرو
Chen Meng'er and Tao Zhi.
تشنغ مينغ'ر وتاو تشي
Successfully matched.
تم اختيار بعضهم البعض بنجاح
Team formation successful.
تم تشكيل الفرق بنجاح
For islanders who didn't match in the first round,
المتسابقون الذين لم يتوفقوا في الجولة الأولى
groupings will be decided based on female islanders' choices.
سيتم تقسيمهم بناءً على اختيار الفتيات
That's okay then.
هذا جيد إذًا
All teams please proceed to the survival arena.
يرجى من جميع الفرق التوجه إلى ساحة البقاء
To begin the final
البدء في آخر مرة
partner mission for off-island invitation rights.
مهمة الشراكة لمنح حق موعد خارج الجزيرة
What game is today?
ما هي لعبة اليوم؟
Don't know.
لا أعلم
Here we go again—the Colosseum.
ها هو الساحة مجددًا
Right, we should keep a low profile today.
صحيح، اليوم يجب أن نكون أكثر هدوءًا
Yeah, just go easy.
نعم، استسلمنا بالفعل
Everyone actually wants to go on an off-island date.
الجميع في الحقيقة يريد موعدًا خارج الجزيرة
So we should give the chance to others.
لذا يجب أن نمنح الفرصة للآخرين
So in the end, we decided that—
لذلك قررنا في النهاية
We’ll still play the game,
سنشارك في اللعبة كالعادة
but without being too aggressive.
لكن لن نكون هجوميين جدًا
Let’s just take it easy.
سنكتفي بذلك فقط
Today, we’ll give others—
اليوم، نتركها للآخرين
Okay.
حسنًا
Since Xiao Enya and I already went on a date,
لأنني خرجت في موعد مع شياو أنيا بالفعل
we actually want to pass this chance
في الحقيقة نود أن نعطي هذه الفرصة
to those who need it more.
لمن هم بحاجة إليها أكثر منا
What is this?
ما هذا
Let's pull that thing.
اسحب ذلك الشيء
Like tearing name tags.
مثل تمزيق الشعار
No way, oh my god.
لا أصدق، يا إلهي
Yes, must tear.
نعم، يجب أن نمزق
Must tear.
يجب تمزيقه
I'm dizzy, I can't beat others like this.
دوّخت، لا أستطيع هزيمتهم
The Final Off-Island Date Rights Battle of Tianping Island
معركة حاسمة لحق موعد خارج الجزيرة في ميزان التفضيل
The showdown is imminent
على وشك البدء
This round consists of two stages
هذه الجولة تتكون من مرحلتين
In the Love Chase competition
خلال سباق القلوب
The top four pairs
أول أربع ثنائيات
Will advance to the Fencing Defense battle
ستتأهل إلى معركة الدفاع
For the final showdown
وتخوض الجولة النهائية
To win the last off-island date opportunity
للفوز بآخر حق موعد خارج الجزيرة
Warriors charging for love
يا أبطال تسعون من أجل الحب
Are you ready?
هل أنتم مستعدون؟
We're ready!
مستعدون
Now announcing the rules for Stage One
سنعلن الآن عن المرحلة الأولى
Rules of the Love Chase game
قوانين لعبة سباق القلوب
Female participants from each team
كل فتاة في الفريق
Will wear vests with three heart symbols
سترتدي سترة بثلاث قلوب
Male participants will attempt
والشباب سيهاجمون قلوب باقي الفرق
To remove others' hearts
يبدؤون الهجوم
While protecting their own hearts
بينما يحمون قلوب فريقهم
From being removed
لكي لا تُنتزع
If all three hearts are removed
إذا نُزعت القلوب الثلاثة
The team is eliminated
يتم إقصاء كامل الفريق
The last four surviving pairs
آخر أربع ثنائيات باقية
Will advance to the next round
يُؤهلون للمرحلة التالية
Be careful - just don't get hurt
انتبهوا، لا تتعرضوا للأذى فقط
We can do this
يمكننا ذلك
I'll give it my all
سأبذل قصارى جهدي
No matter what it takes
مهما كان الأمر
To win this final date opportunity
يجب أن أفوز بحق الموعد الأخير
Because I want
لأني أرغب في الخروج مع
To go on a date with the guy I like
الشاب الذي يعجبني
And get to know everything about him
وأتعرف عليه بشكل أفضل
It's too loose
فضفاضة جداً
This will have to do
هذا ما يمكن فعله
Because when we play games
خلال لعبنا دائماً
We actually have good chemistry
كنا متفاهمين فعلاً
And we'd like
ونفكر أيضاً
If we win this game
لو فزنا في هذه الجولة
To go off-island together
سنخرج معاً خارج الجزيرة
I want to fight for this off-island date
أريد الفوز بحق موعد خارج الجزيرة
Because I really want to go
حقاً أريد أن أذهب مع دانيال
Explore the outside world with Daniel
لنرى العالم خارجاً
I want to win this for myself
أريد أن أحقق انتصاراً لنفسي
If we get this chance
إذا حصلت على هذه الفرصة
I'd love to take
أتمنى أن أصطحب
Weng Fanqian out somewhere fun
ونغ فانشي للخروج معاً
This is so frustrating
أشعر بالحزن
This game gives me no advantage
هذه اللعبة ليست لصالحني أبداً
It's okay
لا عليك
I'm absolutely
أنا فعلاً
Determined to seize this opportunity
أطمح بقوة لهذه الفرصة، نعم
I most want you to leave the island
أتمنى حقاً أن تغادر الجزيرة
I won't mess with you
لن أهاجمك
Okay
حسناً
Form an alliance
تحالف
Agreed
موافق
The three of us will ally
سنتحالف نحن الثلاثة
Deal
حسناً
Then it's settled
تحالف إذاً
We'll protect one together
اثنان يحمون واحداً
Because I want to protect Zheng Dedong
لأنني أود حماية تشنغ ددونغ
Want him to have a chance for an off-island date
أريده أن يحصل على فرصة موعد خارجي
We'll fight for this opportunity for Zheng Dedong
سأقاتل هذه الجولة من أجل تشنغ ددونغ
Three teams alliance
تحالف بين ثلاث فرق
All three of their teams have allied
هم الثلاثة تحالفوا
Then let's form a four-team alliance
فلنتحالف نحن الأربعة
Then our four teams together
نحن أربعة فرق معاً
Right, let's just eliminate those three
نعم، ونطردهم الثلاثة مباشرة
Done deal
هكذا ننتهي
This way all four of our teams advance
وبهذا نتأهل جميعنا
All islanders, please prepare
استعدوا يا سكان الجزيرة
Three
ثلاثة
Two
اثنان
One
واحد
Begin
ابدأوا
Then I'll tear it
سأبدأ بالتمزيق
Tearing begins
بدأت التمزقات
Right, stand together
نعم، قفوا معاً
Why target us first?
لماذا نحن أولاً؟
Go, I'll pull you over
تعال، سأجرك إلي
Please, don't mess with me.
أرجوك، لا تهجم علي
Beautiful
جميل
Be careful
احذر
Gu Zhenxiang, go over there
غو تشنشيانغ، اذهب إلى هناك
Sorry
آسف
Fang Xu, you lost
غو شي، لقد خسرت
"Help!"
"النجدة"
I'm sorry, I'm truly sorry
آسف جداً، حقاً آسف
We have no connection, none at all
لا بأس، ليس بيننا مشكلة
Right, we don't care
نعم، لا مشكلة عندنا
Listen, I won't attack anyone
أخبرك، لن أهاجم أحداً
But I will protect her
سأحميها فقط
Attack as you please
هاجموا أنتم كما تشاؤون
Come closer
اقتربوا
I'm going that way
سأذهب إلى هناك
I'll defend
سأتولى الدفاع
We're peaceful
سنتخذها بهدوء
Daniel's back again
دانيال عاد مجدداً
You really have no class
لا يوجد لديكم مستوى فعلاً
Don't mess with me
لا تهاجمني
Run!
اركض
I think my teammate is quite manly.
أظن أن زميلي رجل فعلاً
From the very beginning,
منذ البداية
he tried his best to protect me behind him.
يحاول دائماً أن يحميني خلفه
And he would go all out
ويبذل قصارى جهده أيضاً
to fight against others.
في مواجهة الآخرين
I think he's really striving to win first place.
شعرت أنه يكافح لنيل المركز الأول
putting in enough effort.
ويبذل مجهوداً كافياً
Can you target someone else first?
هاجم الآخرين أولاً، حسناً؟
No more.
انتهت
No choice.
لا حل آخر
You're it.
حان دورك
Sorry about this.
آسف
I was also attacked by Gu Zhenxiang.
تعرضت لهجوم من غو تشنشيانغ أيضاً
Game over.
انتهت اللعبة
You're down.
سقطت
I'm down.
سقطت أنا أيضاً
I'm knocked out, seriously.
ذهلت فعلاً، يا إلهي
You okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
I'm fine.
لا بأس
He shouldn't have teamed up with us, actually.
لم يكن يجب أن يكون معنا بالفريق
Right.
صحيح
He should've teamed up with them.
كان يجدر به أن يكون بفريقهم
We dragged you down.
نحن من أوقعك بالمشكلة
Not at all.
لا أبداً
After all, it's the last time.
لأنها آخر فرصة لنا
And Weng Fanqian really wanted to go out.
وأيضاً ونغ فانشي تريد الخروج
Since I didn't get the island date privilege,
لأنني لم أفز بحق موعد خارج الجزيرة
it's just a bit regrettable.
لدي بعض الندم
Congratulations Chen Mengjia and Gu Zhenxiang
مبروك لتشنغ مونجيا وغو تشنشيانغ
Chen Menger and Tao Zhi
تشنغ مونغ أر وتاو تشي
He Jinyi and Daniel
خه جيني ودانيال
Lu Wanfei and Fu Jie
لو وانفاي وفو جيا
Now entering the second stage: Fencing Defense Battle
تأهلوا إلى معركة الدفاع في المرحلة الثانية
Fencing
المبارزة
Go for it!
هيا!
Now announcing the game rules
سنعلن الآن القوانين
Four teams will be grouped through rock-paper-scissors
تقسم الفرق الأربع عبر قرعة الأبيض والأسود
Each group will duel against another
كل مجموعة ستتبارى مع الأخرى
The girls will be responsible for offense
الفتيات مسؤولات عن الهجوم
Using color-tipped fists
باستخدام قبضة ملونة
to attack the boys' protective gear
يضربن الزي الدفاعي للشباب
Each round, if a boy gets
في كل جولة، على الشباب
three colored marks on him
إذا حصلوا على ثلاث علامات ملونة
he will be eliminated
يعتبرون خارج التحدي
Please give it your all
ابذلوا جهدكم جميعاً
to win the final off-island date privilege
للفوز بآخر حق موعد خارج الجزيرة
Okay, leave it to me
حسناً، اتركوها لي
Let's play rock-paper-scissors
لنقم بقرعة الأبيض والأسود
There are too many people
عدد الأشخاص كبير
Let's have each team send one person
فليرسل كل فريق شخصاً واحداً
to play rock-paper-scissors
هكذا نقوم بالقرعة
Then you girls
أيتها الفتيات
come play rock-paper-scissors
تعالين للقرعة
I'll be a team by myself
أنا فريق بمفردي
You go first
اخرجي أولاً
Rock-paper-scissors
قرعة أبيض وأسود
Those two versus us two
هم اثنان، ونحن اثنان
Chen Menger and Chen Mengjia are hilarious
تشنغ مونغ أر وتشنغ مونجيا مضحكتان
Lu Wanfei & Fu Jie vs. He Jinyi & Daniel
لو وانفاي وفو جيا يواجهان خه جيني ودانيال
Begin
ابدأوا
Okay
حسناً
Charge
اندفعوا!
Go, Lu Wanfei!
هيا يا لو وانفاي!
Go for it!
هيا!
Look
شاهد
Lu Wanfei and Fu Jie score one point.
لو وانفاي وفو جيا حصلا على نقطة
That guy is too passive, doesn't create much space.
الشاب سلبي جداً، لا مساحة لديه
His reach is long—that's an advantage.
ذراعه طويل، هذه ميزة
No
لا يصلح
He Jinyi is at a disadvantage
خه جيني ليس له أفضلية
What can I even block?
ماذا يمكنني أن أصد هنا؟
It's fine
لا بأس
Go Lu Wanfei!
هيا يا لو وانفاي
Don't let it affect your friendship.
لا تدعوا ذلك يؤثر على المشاعر
Just have fun.
استمتعوا باللعب فقط
Safety first.
السلامة أولاً
Round two begins.
بدأت الجولة الثانية
Go for it!
هيا!
Lu Wanfei and Fu Jie score two points.
لو وانفاي وفو جيا حصلا على نقطتين
This is...
وهذا أيضاً...
This is a bit... there's nothing...
هذا أيضاً بلا جدوى تقريباً
Give it your all.
ضاعفوا الحماس
Show some energy.
أظهروا طاقتكم
I can't go, it's not that I don't want to.
لا أستطيع الذهاب، ليس لأني لا أريد
The third round begins.
بدأت الجولة الثالثة
No
لا يمكن
Lu Wanfei has long arms
ذراعا لو وانفي طويلتان
Her arms are too long
ذراعاها طويلتان جدًا
Lu Wanfei and Fu Jie win
لو وانفي وفو جيه فازا
Lu Wanfei, you're amazing
لو وانفي، أنتِ مذهلة
How did Fu Jie win without effort?
كيف فاز فو جيه بسهولة
Fu Jie
فو جيه
Fu Jie wins effortlessly again
فو جيه فاز بسهولة مرة أخرى
Lu Wanfei and Fu Jie win
لو وانفي وفو جيه انتصرا
Happiness came too suddenly
السعادة جاءت فجأة جدًا
Stop talking
لا تتكلم أكثر
Fu Jie
فو جيه
Always getting carried
دائمًا أُنقَل إلى الفوز
It's fine, no problem
لا بأس، الأمر بسيط
The height difference is just unfair
الفرق في الطول جعل الأمر غير عادل
Their build is just like that
بنضطر نقبل بالبنية الجسدية
He Jinyi is so tiny
وخه جنيي صغيرة جدًا
While Lu Wanfei is so much taller
ولو وانفي أطول منها بكثير
So there's no helping it
لهذا لا يوجد حل
Chen Mengjia vs. Gu Zhenxiang
تشن مونغ جيا وغو تشنشيانغ
Versus Chen Meng'er and Tao Zhi
ضد تشن مونغ إر وتاو تشي
Begin
ابدأوا
Okay
حسنًا
Their body types happen to be quite similar
أجسامهن متشابهة تمامًا
Alright
موافق
Evenly matched
القوة متساوية
This is what you call an evenly matched duel
هذه المواجهة متكافئة فعلًا
The two of them
هما الاثنتان
Go for it
هيا
Chen Mengjia and Gu Zhenxiang score a point.
تشن مونغ جيا وغو تشنشيانغ حصلا على نقطة
Chen Mengjia is so fierce.
تشن مونغ جيا قوية
You're so strong.
لديك طاقة كبيرة
So powerful.
طاقة هائلة فعلًا
She's strong, really strong.
هي قوية، حقًا قوية
Go for it!
شدي حيلك
Round two begins.
الجولة الثانية تبدأ
Keep it up!
تشجيع
Chen Mengjia is unstoppable.
تشن مونغ جيا قوية جدًا
Go Chen Meng'er!
شدي حيلك، تشن مونغ إر
You can do it!
هيا
Fight on!
استمري
Let's go!
تشجيع
One to one
واحد مقابل واحد
I'll go first
سأبدأ أنا
Chen Mengjia first
تشن مونغ جيا تبدأ أولًا
Chen Mengjia and Gu Zhenxiang score two points.
تشن مونغ جيا وغو تشنشيانغ حصلا على نقطتين
Chen Mengjia is amazing.
تشن مونغ جيا رائعة
I'm sorry.
آسفة
No need to apologize.
لا داعي للاعتذار
Is there any special technique?
هل هناك خدعة؟
There's no special technique for this.
لا يوجد خدعة هنا
Round three begins.
الجولة الثالثة تبدأ
Go Chen Meng'er! Go Chen Meng'er!
تشن مونغ إر، هيا!
Go for it!
شدي حيلك
Keep it up!
استمري
This competitive spirit.
رغبة الفوز هذه
Chen Mengjia and Gu Zhenxiang win.
تشن مونغ جيا وغو تشنشيانغ فازا
No choice.
لا حيلة
There's no room to maneuver here.
لا مجال للحركة هنا
Either step down.
إما تنسحب
Or stay there and get poked.
أو تنتظر أن يخترقك الخصم
Great job, very powerful.
ممتاز، طاقة قوية
Congratulations to Lu Wanfei and Fu Jie.
مبروك للو وانفي وفو جيه
Chen Mengjia and Gu Zhenxiang.
وتشن مونغ جيا وغو تشنشيانغ
Have earned the right to the last off-island date.
حصلوا على حق الموعد الأخير خارج الجزيرة
Now please have all island teams proceed.
الآن على كل فريق من سكان الجزيرة
Go to the supply room to choose your rewards.
الذهاب لمخزن المؤن واختيار مكافأتهم
I'll go to the supply room first.
سأذهب لمخزن المؤن أولًا
This game was made for you.
هذه اللعبة مصممة لك
Check the bulletin board.
انظر إلى لوحة الإعلانات
We can choose two.
يمكننا اختيار اثنين
Two items.
قطعتان من المؤن
Let's just get cola, I think.
لنأخذ الكولا جميعنا، برأيي
Okay.
حسنًا
Nothing else worth taking.
لا يوجد شيء مغرٍ لآخذه
I want to drink - I want sugar-free.
أريد شرب واحدة، أريدها بدون سكر
Grab some nuts to eat.
خذ بعض المكسرات
Want a Snickers?
هل تريد سنيكرز؟
Snickers then.
سنيكرز إذًا
Here.
تفضل
The three teams that didn't enter.
الفرق الثلاثة التي لم تدخل
Get one (item). Okay.
تحصل على قطعة واحدة من المؤن، حسنًا
Get one for Weng Fanxi.
خذ واحدة لـ ونغ فانشي
Eat this - shredded beef jerky.
كل هذا، لحم بقري مجفف
We're going for sharing.
نحن قررنا المشاركة
Forty-five grams of protein.
خمسة وأربعون غرامًا من البروتين
Fu Jie will love this.
فو جيه سيحبها
Share it with them.
شاركهم بها
But the first bite is mine.
لكن أول قضمة لي
Of course.
طبعًا
Open it first.
افتح أولًا
You open it first.
افتح أنت أولًا
Isn't this shot beautiful?
أليست هذه الصورة جميلة؟
Is there something behind?
هل هناك شيء في الخلف؟
Will it be backlit?
هل سيكون هناك ضوء خلفي؟
Backlighting is beautiful - I'm against the light.
الإضاءة الخلفية أجمل، أنا ضد الضوء
Turn slightly like this.
امِل قليلًا هكذا
Like this.
هكذا
Here.
تفضل
Princess, please eat.
أيتها الأميرة، تفضلي
Please have some meat.
تفضلي اللحم
So full, I want to burp now.
أنا شبعانة، أريد أن أتجشأ
There actually aren't that many.
في الواقع، ليست كثيرة
Share with your bros.
وزعها على أصدقائك المقربين
Okay.
حسنًا
Pretty tasty.
طعمه لذيذ
I'm starting to feel reluctant to leave this place
بدأت أشعر بعدم الرغبة في الرحيل
I think after we go back
أشعر أننا عندما نعود لاحقًا
when we remember this place
عندما نتذكر هذا المكان
it'll feel like a dream
سيبدو وكأننا كنا نحلم
just an eleven-day dream
كأننا حلمنا أحد عشر يومًا
All those intense emotions we felt
شعرنا بمشاعر كبيرة وقتها
will be gone, probably only remembering
لكن لاحقًا ستختفي وستبقى الذكريات
a few sunsets
بعض الغروب فقط
But I'll only remember you and me
على أي حال، أتذكر أنا وأنت فقط
Every day of my new age
كل يوم في عامك الجديد
was spent with you
قضيته معك
I'm still quite curious
ما زلتُ فضوليًا
about your thoughts and such
أفكارك وكلامك
I think there are quite a lot
أعتقد أنها كثيرة
of ups and downs, conflicts, changes, and such
هناك تقلبات وصراعات وتغييرات
But
لكن...
setting those aside
لو تركنا ذلك جانبًا
just making a sincere choice is enough, I think
يكفي أن تختار بصدق
Yeah, I just go with my feelings, you know
صحيح، فقط أمشي وراء إحساسي
Because my own emotions aren't very stable
لأن مشاعري غير مستقرة كثيرًا
so my first requirement in choosing a partner
لذلك أول شرط حين أبحث عن شريك
is that they must be emotionally stable
أن تكون مشاعره ثابتة
You're very stable
وأنتَ مستقر جدًا
Can you take a couple photos for me first, please?
ساعدني في التقاط صورتين أولًا، حسنًا؟
I don't want to take photos for you.
لا أريد أن ألتقط لك صورًا
Be good and hurry up.
كن مطيعًا، أسرع
Beg me.
ترجاني
Please.
أترجاك
Okay.
حسنًا
Don't worry, I'm professional at this.
لا تقلق، أنا محترف
Alright? Tell me when you press it.
حسنًا؟ أخبرني حين تضغط
Pressed it.
ضغطت
Come show me.
تعال لأريك
Looks good.
ممتاز
What I mean is we could take another one in portrait.
أقصد التقط واحدة بالطول أيضًا
Wait a second, hold on.
انتظر، انتظر قليلًا
So annoying.
مزعج جدًا
Getting irritated.
أصبحتُ عصبية
I'm already starting to...
بالنسبة لي بدأ...
Not as enthusiastic as before.
لم يعد هناك شغف كما من قبل
Done.
انتهى
Here you go.
تفضل
Take another one closer.
التقط واحدة أخرى أقرب
Just messing with you.
أمزح معك
Looks nice.
جميلة
Absolutely gorgeous.
جميلة جدًا
You're so good at taking photos.
تصويرك رائع
So fake.
تظاهري بالموت مبالغ فيه
It's all in my eyes, ugh.
العرق دخل في عيني كلها
Let's go to the beach.
هيّا إلى الشاطئ
Right.
نعم
Nice, very nice.
حسنًا، جميلة
Is this okay?
هل هذا مقبول؟
Okay, one more.
حسنًا، واحدة أخرى
Looks good.
جميلة
Really beautiful, so pretty.
جميلة حقًا، رائعة
You look handsome today.
لباسك اليوم أنيق جدًا
Okay.
حسنًا
Let's go eat.
لنذهب للأكل
Tell me right away if you did something wrong.
لم تخبرني فورًا بخطئك
Let's check out the fitness
دعنا نرى التمارين
Look, have a seat
انظر، اجلس قليلًا
Are you feeling a little down?
هل تشعر بالقليل من الحزن؟
Me?
أنا؟
I’m really okay.
حقًا، أنا بخير
I just feel like in these last few days,
أعتقد أن الأيام القليلة المتبقية
spending more time with everyone
سأقضيها مع الجميع أكثر
is really nice.
هذا جيد
Actually, today when I was gaming,
بصراحة اليوم وأنا ألعب
I wasn’t even that competitive.
رغبتي في التفوق اليوم لم تكن قوية
Have you ever thought
هل فكرتَ أبدًا...
about the last day
ماذا بشأن اليوم الأخير؟
On the last day, what...
اليوم الأخير، ماذا؟
Do you have any different thoughts?
هل لديك أفكار مختلفة؟
I think...
أظن أنني...
I might have some...
قد يكون لدي بعض...
Some regrets, I suppose.
أشعر ببعض الندم، أظن ذلك
Well...
فقط...
What I've always wanted to say is
كنت دائمًا أرغب في قول هذا من قبل
I hope everyone can
أتمنى أن يتمكن الجميع
during these last few days
خلال هذه الأيام الأخيرة
without holding anything back
أن يتكلموا دون تحفظ
say everything you want to say here
ويقولوا كل ما يرغبون بقوله هنا
and leave with no regrets
حتى لا يندموا على شيء
No
لا
I don't dare
لا أجرؤ
Why wouldn't you dare?
ولماذا لا تجرؤ؟
Some things you say might have consequences
هناك أمور إذا قلتها قد تترتب عليها نتائج
that you might not be able to handle
لا يمكنك تحملها أحيانًا
So some things just
بعض الأشياء بالفعل
just can't be said
لا يمكن
They won't be spoken
لا يمكن قولها ببساطة
They won't be said
لن أقولها
Right
صحيح
After spending all these days together
هل شعرت بعد كل هذه الأيام معًا
have you ever felt attracted to someone?
أنك تأثرت عاطفيًا؟
Not necessarily
لا أقصد تلك المشاعر التي
to the point of full-blown liking
تصل حد الحب فعليًا
But yes, there was
نعم، حدث ذلك
Then I think that's good
إذًا أعتقد أن هذا جيد
Actually, that's really nice
في الحقيقة، هذا رائع
But I think these kinds of feelings
لكن أظن أن هذه الأمور أحيانًا
don't necessarily need to be spoken
ليست ضروريًا أن تُقال
It's just...
يعني...
Yes, right
نعم، صحيح
Actually, what I think now is
صراحةً، فكرتي الآن هي
I just hope we'll all have
أتمنى أن نحظى مستقبلًا
more chances to gather in the future
بفرص أكثر لنجتمع معًا
Yes
صحيح
Right
نعم
I think it's actually quite difficult
أرى أن ذلك ليس سهلًا أبدًا
Hard... it might be hard to get everyone together
صعب جدًا أن يجتمع الجميع سويًا
But perhaps
لكن ربما
if there's hope, if there's a chance
إذا وُجد أمل أو فرصة
I think I'll really miss everyone here
سأشتاق للجميع هنا كثيرًا
Maybe...
ربما
On your first day
في اليوم الأول لك
you weren't saying this on days two and three
الكلام اختلف في اليوم الثاني والثالث
It's been so long now
لقد مر وقت طويل
Shouldn't I have changed somewhat?
أليس من الطبيعي أن أتغير قليلاً؟
I hope after this is over
أتمنى بعد انتهاء البرنامج
I can still ask you
أن أبقى على تواصل معك
for recommendations on good anime
لأسألك عن أنميات جيدة
Sure, of course
أكيد، طبعًا يمكنك ذلك
Besides gaming and reading manga
بعيدًا عن الألعاب أو المانجا
tell me another hobby of yours
اخبرني عن هواية أخرى لديك
I just love trying good food from different places
أحب أن أجرّب الأكلات الطيبة في أماكن جديدة
I'm similar but different from you
أشبهك في ذلك لكني مختلف أيضًا
Whenever I visit a new place
كلما أزور مكانًا جديدًا
I might not try the most famous local food
أحيانًا لا أجرب أشهر الأطعمة هناك
but I'll definitely visit
لكنني حتمًا أزور هناك
the most famous gym there
أشهر صالة رياضية
So if you meet a girl at the gym
إذا قابلت فتاة في الجيم
would you proactively ask for her contact?
هل تذهب لتطلب وسيلة تواصل منها؟
Probably not, I think
لا أعتقد أنني سأفعل ذلك
Would you instead
هل ستكون المبادر
try to correct her form?
وتقوم بتعليمها الوضعيات الصحيحة؟
I wouldn't do that either
لن أفعل ذلك أيضًا
That would be really unnecessary
هذا تصرف زائد عن الحد
I really dislike when people
أكره من يقوم بذلك أساسًا
proactively come over to correct others
يأتي ليعلم الآخرين دون طلب
Right
صحيح
That's such a turn-off at the gym
هذا تصرف في الجيم غريب جدًا
Exactly
بالضبط
When two people are mutually curious about each other
الفضول المتبادل بين شخصين فقط
they'll naturally glance at each other
هو ما يدفعهم للنظر لبعضهم
So we're talking about
ثم نبدأ الحديث
what you'd do at the gym
وأثناء التمارين في الجيم
if you meet someone you like
إذا صادفت شخصًا يعجبك ماذا تفعل؟
Have you experienced this?
هل حدث ذلك معك من قبل؟
Someone like me wouldn't dare
أنا شخص لا أجرؤ على هذا
I'm going to work out.
أذهب فقط لأتمرن
You seemed a bit unhappy this afternoon
بدوت حزينًا ظهر هذا اليوم
No
لا، ليس كذلك
Really?
حقًا؟
Just a bit of a system freeze, you know
كنت فقط تائه الذهن، كما تعلم
It's fine, no problem
لا بأس، الأمر عادي
Working out while chatting with you
أستطيع الدردشة معكم وأتمرن معًا
Killing two birds with one stone
دون أن أضحي بأي منهما
A master of time management
خبير في إدارة الوقت
I'm already balancing everything and managing time
أنا أجمع بين كل شيء بإدارة الوقت
Pretty good
جميل
This is really unbearable
الحياة أحيانًا صعبة جدًا
Forget it, I feel a bit embarrassed.
حسنًا، أشعر بالحرج قليلاً
What's there to be embarrassed about?
ولماذا تخجل؟
It's not like you've never been filmed working out before.
ليست أول مرة يتم تصويرك أثناء التمارين
People say I'm too muscular.
يقول الجميع إنني ضخم جدًا
There seems to be a little light
وتبدو هناك إضاءة تلمع
Is there more?
هل ما زال هناك؟
It can still reach here
ما زالت الإضاءة تظهر
What color are you planning to wear tomorrow?
أي لون ستلبس غدًا؟
Let's eat
تناول الطعام
So today I wanted to "take care" of Chen Mengjia first
لذا أريد اليوم "إخراج" تشن منغجيا أولًا
That was the plan
هذه هي استراتيجيتي
But
ولكن
Plans can't keep up with changes
الخطة لا تواكب التغيرات
Exactly
بالضبط
When I saw you were in a bad mood
عندما وجدت أن مزاجك ليس جيدًا
I asked Xiao Enya to find Zheng Dedong
طلبت من شياو إينيا أن تذهب لزِheng Dedong
Actually, it's not because
في الحقيقة ليست المشكلة
I didn't get any outing privileges
أنني لم أحصل على أي حق خروج
I just felt that
بل شعرت فقط
I didn't take Weng Fanxi out to play one last time
أنه حتى آخر مرة لم آخذ وِنغ فانسي للخارج
But she wanted to go out
رغم أنها أرادت الخروج
For me, it doesn't matter
أما بالنسبة لي، لا يهمني الأمر
This is right outside my home
أنا هنا كأنني بجوار منزلي
I can come out to play anytime
يمكنني الخروج متى أردت
There's still tomorrow on the island
غدًا هناك أنشطة داخل الجزيرة
We'll see.
سنتحدث حينها
So these past few days you've been submitting...
إذًا في الأيام الماضية أصواتك
All to Weng Fanxi.
ذهبت كلها لـ ونغ فانسي
Only two left now.
تبقّى لي رمزان فقط
Who else can I submit to?
لمن يمكنني التصويت غيرها؟
Are you just eating now?
هل أكلت لتوك؟
I came to find you halfway through my meal.
كنت أتناول الطعام وجئت إليك في منتصفه
Why so much smoked meat today?
لماذا هناك الكثير من اللحم المدخن اليوم؟
Do you want to eat my meat?
هل تريد أن تأكل من لحمي؟
No, I mean...
لا، قصدي...
I still have half my meat left uneaten.
ما زال عندي نصف قطعة لم أنتهِ منها
Should I bring it over for you?
هل أحضرها لتأكلها؟
No need.
لا داعي
It's fine.
عادي
No, where's your mind going? Weird.
لا، إلى أين ذهب تفكيرك! غريب
Your wild talk today is making me nervous.
كلامك الجريء اليوم أخافني حقًا
Let's eat.
تناول طعامك
What about our Zheng Dedong?
ماذا عن زِheng Dedong لدينا؟
Is he okay?
هل هو بخير؟
He should be fine.
أعتقد أنه بخير
What I mean is...
أعني بـ "ينبغي"
Although he might be a little sad,
رغم أنه ربما حزين قليلًا
he can still get through
لكنه يستطيع أن يعيش اليوم بهدوء
today peacefully.
ويكمل يومه
Did you see his back today?
هل رأيت ظهره اليوم؟
Do you know what it looked like
هل تعلم كيف بدا لي ظهره للتو؟
when I saw him earlier?
كيف كان شكله برأيك؟
He might feel some regret
قد يشعر بالندم قليلاً.
Having regrets is okay
لا بأس أن يكون هناك بعض الندم.
It's not like we'll disappear after leaving the island
ليس كأنك ستختفي بعد مغادرة الجزيرة.
Vanish into thin air
لن تتبخر من العالم.
I told him
لقد تحدثت معه.
I said if there's anything you want to say later
قلت له إذا كان لديك شيء تود قوله
You can just message me on WeChat
يمكنك مراسلتي على ويشات مباشرة.
That means we won't contact each other - that's terrible
هذا يعني عدم التواصل، انتهى الأمر.
This sounds very insecure
يبدو هذا تصرفاً يفتقد للأمان.
This sounds like a very ordinary friendship
يبدو كصديق عادي فقط.
If it were me
لو كنت مكاني،
I would want to hear something like
كنت أود سماع عبارة
"Let's keep in touch after leaving the island"
"لنواصل تواصلنا بعد مغادرة الجزيرة".
And I'd want to stay in Hainan for a few days
وأود أيضًا البقاء في هاينان بضعة أيام.
"Could you show me around?"
هل يمكنك أن تدلني على بعض الأماكن؟
I'd want to hear that kind of thing
أرغب بسماع مثل هذا الكلام.
But I don't know about you two
لكن لا أعرف وضعكما.
I don't dare
لا أستطيع.
Is it that you don't dare, or you don't want to?
هل لا تجرؤ أم لا تريد؟
I do want to
أريد ذلك.
But I'm not entirely sure
ولكنني لست متأكداً تماماً.
I'm uncertain about these feelings
لست واثقة من طبيعة مشاعري.
What exactly they mean
ولا أعرف سببها الحقيقي.
So I hope to wait until after we leave the island
لهذا أريد الانتظار لما بعد الجزيرة.
When my mind is clearer
عندما يهدأ عقلي وأفكر بوضوح.
If I still feel the same way
إذا بقي إحساسي كما هو،
Then we can talk about it then
سأتحدث عن الأمر لاحقاً.
I overthink things
أنا أفكر كثيراً بالأمور.
I don't dare to say certain things now
لا أجرؤ على قول بعض الأشياء الآن
Really
كثيراً...
Promising words
وعود كبيرة.
I'm also afraid of hurting him
وأخشى أيضاً أن أجرحه.
It's not that I don't like him, but I have doubts.
أنا لا أكره الأمر، لكن لدي تردد.
It's not that I dislike him.
ليس أنني لا أحبه،
I don't like him.
لو لم يكن يعجبني،
I wouldn't have talked with him for so long.
لما تحدثت معه كل هذه الفترة.
Nor would I care about him.
ولما اهتممت لأمره.
Then there must be some affection.
أكيد ثمة إعجاب.
There must be affection.
بالتأكيد هناك إعجاب.
At the beginning when we got close,
منذ البداية اقتربت منه.
I was the one who initiated conversations with Zheng Dedong first.
أنا من بدأت الحديث مع تشنغ ديدونغ.
Back then, I valued three people more.
كان هناك ثلاثة كانوا يهمونني أكثر.
Chen Guanyu, Fu Jie, and Zheng Dedong.
تشين غوانيو، فو جيه، وتشينغ ديدونغ.
I took time to understand each of them.
تعرفت عليهم جميعاً.
And in the end, it turned out to be
وفي النهاية،
Zheng Dedong.
كان تشنغ ديدونغ هو الأهم.
Both he and I are the type who overthink things.
كلانا أشخاص كثيرو التفكير.
But his personality is slightly more reserved than mine.
هو أكثر تحفظًا مني قليلاً.
He's the type who won't speak his mind.
من النادر أن يبوح بمشاعره.
At most, he'll show it through actions.
عادة يُظهر مشاعره بالأفعال.
He'll express it that way.
يعبر عن ذاته بالأفعال.
Moreover, he's very sensitive
كما أنه شخص حساس جداً.
and afraid of getting hurt.
ويخشى أن يتأذى.
So he'd rather not say anything.
لذلك يفضل كتمان مشاعره.
From a guy's perspective,
من منظور رجل،
this level of disappointment must mean he likes her.
شدة حزنه تدل على أنه مهتم حقاً.
Then are you willing to try?
هل تودين المحاولة؟
I...
أنا...
Because you haven't tried.
بما أنك لم تجربي،
How would you know if it works or not?
كيف ستعرفين إن كان ذلك سينجح؟
There's not even a fifty percent chance anymore.
حتى احتمال ٥٠٪ لم يعد موجوداً.
But if he's willing to be brave today,
لو كان اليوم شجاعًا
would you consider it?
هل ستفكرين بالأمر؟
How exactly would he be brave?
كيف يكون شجاعاً؟
By being more willing to share his thoughts with you.
يعني أن يكون أكثر صراحة معك.
Then I might consider it more carefully.
سأفكر وقتها بالأمر بجدية أكبر.
Looking at our patterns,
انظر إلى أسلوبنا المختلف.
they're completely different.
أسلوبانا مختلفان تمامًا.
So that's why...
ولهذا السبب
it's easy to miss opportunities like this.
من السهل أن يفوت الواحد الفرصة.
What do you think?
ما رأيكم أنتم؟
Your relationship
ما مصير علاقتكما
what will happen after leaving the island?
بعد مغادرة الجزيرة؟
I think it will be tested
أعتقد أنها ستواجه اختباراً.
Definitely
بالتأكيد ستمر باختبار.
That is... there are indeed differences
هناك بالفعل اختلاف واضح.
Actually, I feel a lot of pressure
بصراحة، أشعر أنني مضغوطة للغاية.
Because I
لأنني
am someone who moves at a slower pace
أنا شخص يحب الإيقاع البطيء.
At present
حالياً
I still have doubts
ما زلت مرتبكة بمشاعري.
about these feelings of mine
لدي بعض الشكوك حولها.
So I might use
ربما خلال
these last two remaining days
اليومين المتبقيين
to carefully consider this decision
سأفكر جيداً في قراري.
and come up with
ثم أتخذ
an answer that satisfies both myself and others
إجابة ترضيني وترضي الجميع.
But this outfit makes you look
هذا اللباس أظهر شيئًا...
look
أبرز...
older
العمر.
Okay
حسنًا.
Save me a bite
اترك لي قضمة.
You can have it all
كلها لك.
I only ate it because you weren't
أكلت لأنني رأيتك لم تأكلي.
Sis Li, stop sighing, just stop
لا تتحسري أختي، لا داعي لذلك.
I can only share food with
لا أشارك الطعام إلا مع شريكي.
my significant other
نأكل معاً فقط حين يكون هناك علاقة.
Can't do this with anyone else
مع أي شخص آخر، لا أشارك طعامي.
Same for you?
هل أنتِ كذلك أيضاً؟
She must be too
بالطبع هي كذلك.
Yes
نعم.
Thank me
اشكريني!
Sister Chen Mengjia
الأخت تشين منغجيا.
You're such a divine assist
لقد ساعدتِ كثيرًا، بحق!
You know your best quality
تعلمين ما هو أفضل ما فيكِ؟
Is giving enough special favor
أنكِ تمنحين التفضيل الكافي.
This is something all girls love
هذا ما تحبّه جميع الفتيات.
I'm sweating buckets, sis
تعرقت كثيرًا، أختي.
I'll be shy, but still
سأخجل، لكني سأفعل.
Right
نعم.
So this special treatment of yours
لذلك هذا التفضيل عندك
98% of guys can't do
٩٨٪ من الشباب لا يستطيعون فعله.
This recognition
هذا التقدير
98% of guys can't achieve
٩٨٪ من الشباب لا يقدرون عليه.
I think once I take that step
أعتقد عندما أتخذ الخطوة الأولى
Everything will go smoothly
سيصبح كل شيء سهلاً بعدها.
Yes
صحيح.
Xiao Enya
شياو إينيا.
I'm changing clothes
أنا أبدل ملابسي.
I'll wait for you
سأنتظرك.
I notice we're regulars here.
لاحظت أننا دائماً هنا.
Our hearts are here.
قلوبنا هنا دائمًا.
But our bodies are elsewhere.
لكن أجسامنا هناك.
Physically present but mentally absent.
الجسد مكان والقلب مكان آخر.
Okay, that works.
حسنًا، لا بأس.
This is good, let's go.
هذا مناسب، لنذهب.
This one's fine.
هذا جيد.
It matches me well.
يناسبني كثيراً.
This one or that one's better.
هذا أفضل من ذاك.
The long one.
الطويل.
I told you to pick a longer one.
قلت لكِ اختاري الأطول.
Give me the one on your left.
أعطني الجزء الأيسر.
I think this one's better.
أظنه الأنسب.
Longer.
النوع الطويل.
Longer makes your neck appear longer.
الطويل يجعل العنق يبدو أطول.
This makes your back look broad.
هكذا يبدو ظهرك عريضًا.
Who said her back is broad?
من قال أن ظهرها عريض؟
My Xiao Enya has the slimmest back, okay?
شياو إينيا ظهرها أنحف ظهر!
Our Guo Xu is so adorable.
قوه شو رائع للغاية.
Help me touch this up.
عدّل قليلاً لي.
Should we take one of them together?
هل تصور لهما صورة؟
They're so cute together.
هما لطيفان جداً.
So awkward.
لا أعرفهما جيدًا.
Let's go for a natural look.
اجعل الجو يوحي بالعفوية.
An adoring gaze.
نظرة مليئة بالدلال.
Can you look at me adoringly?
هل تنظر لي بنظرة مليئة بالدلال؟
I'll be the one adoring you.
سأنظر إليك بكل دلال.
Try looking at me.
هل تريدني أن أنظر إليك هكذا؟
I can't, this is already killing me.
لا يمكنني ذلك، كأنك قتلتني بالفعل!
No need to adore me.
لا داعي لأن تدللني.
"Help me."
"أنقذوني!"
Like this.
لو تصرفت هكذا...
I like this one best.
هذه الصورة المفضلة عندي.
Guo Xu looks incredibly handsome.
قوه شو رائع للغاية.
Xiao Enya is also a woman.
وشياو إينيا فتاة كذلك.
Why are you trembling?
لماذا هناك ارتجاف؟
How's your arm strength?
هل قوتك جيدة؟
I'm left-handed.
أنا أعسر.
Okay, let me tell you about this angle.
حسنًا، هذا المنظور،
So hot.
الجو حار جدًا.
This one looks good.
هذه الصورة جميلة.
This one is really nice.
هذه أجمل صورة.
Nope.
لا.
My look has a certain charm to it.
هذه الإطلالة فيها لمسة فريدة.
I love this unique charm.
أعجبني هذا الأسلوب المختلف.
This damn charm.
يا لهذه الجاذبية القاتلة!
Dear islanders,
أعزاءنا سكان الجزيرة،
Today's Scale of Preference
ميزان التفضيل لهذا اليوم
is temporarily closed.
سيتوقف مؤقتًا.
The winning islanders,
الرجاء من الفائزين بين سكان الجزيرة
Chen Mengjia, Gu Zhenxiang, Lu Wanfei, and Fu Jie,
تشن منغجيا، قو تشنغشيانغ، لو وانفاي، فو جيه
please proceed to the Scale of Preference in order
الذهاب إلى ميزان التفضيل بالترتيب
to make your off-island date selections.
واختيار حق موعد خارج الجزيرة.
Dear islander,
سكان الجزيرة الأعزاء،
Congratulations on obtaining
نبارك لك الفوز
the final off-island date invitation privilege.
بآخر حق موعد خارج الجزيرة.
Please write the name of your preferred date
اكتب اسم الشخص الذي ترغب بدعوته
on the invitation card.
على بطاقة الدعوة.
Once written, it cannot be changed.
وبمجرد كتابته، لا يمكن التراجع عنه.
This invitation applies to all potential dates.
الدعوة متاحة لجميع الأشخاص من الجنس الآخر.
Please follow your heart in making your choice.
اختر بقلبك ما ترغب فيه.
Wishing you success in your invitation.
نتمنى لك دعوة ناجحة.
Previously, I didn't choose her because of my mistake.
في السابق أخطأت ولم أخترها.
Today, I will definitely choose her.
اليوم سأختارها بالتأكيد.
This is also what I want—
وهذا ما أريده
to fulfill the promise I made to her before.
لأفي بوعدي لها سابقًا.
We'll go on a date.
وسنخرج في موعد معًا.
This time we're still the same old partners
هذه المرة بقينا فريقًا قديمًا معًا
and then won the competition
وفزنا في المسابقة
This island date feels like
أشعر أن موعد الخروج من الجزيرة هذه المرة
on one hand making up for last time's regrets
من جهة لتعويض ما فاتنا في السابق
and on the other hand wanting to give this journey
ومن جهة أخرى لأجل هذه الرحلة
a perfect ending
لأضع نهاية مثالية لها
The final island date
آخر موعد خارج الجزيرة
First we'll definitely play pool
أولًا سنلعب البلياردو بالتأكيد
It's something we both want to do
هذا الشيء أردناه معًا
Then have some drinks and chat
ثم نشرب قليلًا وندردش
I think we'll get to know each other better
أظن علينا أن نتعرف أكثر
I think it'll be a relaxed and enjoyable atmosphere
أعتقد أن الأجواء ستكون مريحة وممتعة
Because we're actually quite close
لأني في الحقيقة أعرفها جيدًا
so I think tomorrow's date
لذا أظن أن موعد الغد
won't have too much pressure
لن يكون فيه عبء كبير
Just have fun playing around
بس نستمتع ونلعب
I'm extremely happy today
أنا اليوم سعيد جدًا
and finally got the chance
وأخيرًا سنحت لي الفرصة
to go on a date with Fujie
للخروج في موعد مع فُو جيه
I've actually always wanted to date him
كنت دائمًا أرغب في موعد معه
but for various reasons
لكن لأسباب متعددة
it just never happened
لم يكن ذلك ممكنًا حتى الآن
Fujie always said he wanted to ride a motorcycle
فو جيه دائمًا يقول أنه يريد ركوب الدراجة
And then
و...
I think I can sit on the back seat
ربما أجلس خلفه في الدراجة
I've confirmed my feelings
تأكدت من مشاعري
I have stronger feelings for you
وأشعر بك أكثر من غيرك
We've watched many sunsets together
شاهدت كثيرًا من الغروب معك
Anyway, I only remember you and me
المهم أني أتذكرنا نحن فقط
Actually, about Weng Fanxi
في الحقيقة أنا تجاه ونغ فان شي
I'm also very interested
أيضًا مهتم جدًا
I hope after this is over
أتمنى بعد انتهاء هذا
I can still
أن أظل أتكلم معك
ask you about good anime recommendations
وأطلب منك ترشيح بعض الأنمي الجيد
Sure, of course
أكيد ممكن
I hope to say everything
أتمنى أن كل ما أريد قوله هنا
I want to say here without regrets
أخبرتك به دون ندم
An off-island date, I really want to go out
حق موعد خارج الجزيرة، أود الخروج فعلًا